(Leonard:)You know, I'm really starting
to not like this guy.
(Penny:)What is your problem?
Do you use up your thinking at work
and have none left for home?
(Raj:)I don't know.
(Leonard:)It's hard sometimes.
(Leonard:)Everywhere you go, guys hit on you.
(Leonard:)Even if I'm standing right there.
(Leonard:)And they're all taller than me.
Why is everyone taller than me?
(Leonard:)You know what, this is all in my head.
(Leonard:)It's my problem, not yours.
(Penny:)Leonard, why do you always do this?
Listen to me. You are the one I'm with.
You know I love you.
(Penny:)So will you please relax
because you're driving me crazy.
(Leonard:)You know, that's the first time you ever said
that you love me.
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Leonard:)We're just supposed to pretend
it's not a big deal?